Software Engineer

Location: Amman-Kalda Telephone: 0096-792807613

Email: hadeel.nawafleh@gmail.com

Professional profile

Strong knowledge in design and integration problem-solving skills. Strong knowledge in PHP (yii, codeignter framework), good knowledge in C#, .NET, AngularJS and MY-SQL with database analysis and design. Skilled in developing business plans, requirements specifications, user documentation, and architectural systems research. Strong written and verbal communications.

IT/Technical skills

php

Java script/type script **AngularJS Software Development** CSS **CASE tools** Mobile application Xml OOP APIs resentful C++ HTML, HTML5 web Design C# **Agile** Linux MVC **Scrum CMS JSON** Team work **Word Press Eclipse** Problem solving skill Communication skills

Bootstrap 4

Varnish SQL /MySQL Quick learner Work under pressure

Career summary

17/1/2018 - 28/2/2019

Bayt.com, Amman Software engineer

I am working with a team on the company's recruitment solution website (www.bayt.com) Maintained and implemented new features on career websites for many different clients Develop software using a variety of technologies, including Linux (Ubuntu), TCL, SVN, PHP, Yii framework, PostgreSQL, JQuery and JavaScript while developing software. Understanding of MVC design patterns, Object Oriented Design and Development

Highly skilled computer engineer / computer technician I have the experience and knowledge in: computer software and hardware installation, web design, graphic design& e-commerce web development. In my job we engage with our principals in managing the maintenance of our customers as well as maintain and develop our inhouse systems. Ability to convert comprehensive layout and wireframes into working HTML pages.

10/2017 - 2/2018National Information Technology (NITC), Amman Software engineer

I worked in network/operation system/tester/it support department at National Information center, I worked with a team on the center recruitment solution website http://www.nitc.gov.jo Maintained and implemented new features on web site using C#, JavaScript, database, and bootstrap.

5/2015 – 12/2015 Academic Entrepreneurship Center of Excellence, Irbid Software engineer

I worked in Develop software using a variety of technologies, including windows, C#, and Windows application, PostgreSQL, JQuery and JavaScript while developing software. Understanding of MVC design patterns, Object Oriented Design and Development During which I worked on the design of Web pages through the use of language html, bootstrap ,C# I have good knowledge in application usage Microsoft (word, Excel, power point)

Education and qualifications_

B.S, Computer Engineer – 2015 (Yarmouk University)